Yes, Ginko committed a grave crime ground.
Ginko is the reason why Tsubikai's dead!
How could you, Ginko?
I'll never forgive you, bears!
I'll ruin you now!
Everyone!
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you.
So, we had to cross the wall.
Kirikuma!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
Kirikuma Orochi!
Girls, this is, like, way bad.
People are saying another bear was here yesterday.
Yeah, but I heard it was exterminated immediately.
That same girl shot it, right?
The one the Invisible Storm isn't a huge fan of?
Yeah, but... and don't tell anyone,
because it's, like, way secret.
Apparently that bear is, like, way still alive.
That's all right, oh!
I
Welcome to the Door to Friendship, Ginko.
You silly girl.
I've finally gotten rid of the nuisance.
Ginko, you're a shiro.
You were the girl Reya gave her pendant to on that stormy night so long ago.
And what a stupid girl you were.
Instead of getting love, you fell into the abyss.
It's all your own fault, dear.
You knew Lulu Yurigasaki loved you, but you pretended not to see.
And then you tried to abandon her.
Now you're paying the price for that sin.
Guess what, Reya?
Reya, your sweet girl, the precious daughter you loved so much is almost mine.
And now I'll make her my bride in the box.
Yes, today.
I'm going to eat Kureha Tsubaki.
Kuro!
I lost it.
You should be thankful you're alive.
For now, at least.
Goodness, did I surprise you?
Why are you here?
I thought you were dead.
Grow, grow.
Well, you thought right because I am dead.
It's crazy, but you're the only one who can see me right now.
Everything's fine.
Just think of me as a ghost named Desire that happens to dwell inside you right here.
Is that explanation enough?
Where are we?
The door to friendship.
The center of the sky that divides the worlds of moon and forest.
This is the place where true love is tested.
Now tell me something, Ginko.
I'm dying to hear how you were the one who killed Sumika Izumino.
I say early tomorrow morning, we come back here.
Then the flower bed can get fixed.
I don't mind helping you at all.
Thanks, Mitsuko.
That's so generous of you.
Great.
We're both in.
Are you meeting us too, Kureha?
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
Who did that?
I sensed something was wrong then.
I had a rival at the school who was also after my Kureha Tsubaki.
A bear in human form other than me.
Well, me and Konami.
If I didn't hurry and make my move, another bear was going to get to her before I could.
So.
Bye.
I'm headed this way.
See you in the morning.
Listen, Sumika.
I have an idea about tomorrow.
Why don't we arrange a surprise for Kureha?
A surprise?
I know someone with lilies in bloom who would probably give us some.
Don't you think she'd love that?
I can pick them up tonight so we can plant them for her.
Really?
Yeah.
It'll be great.
So tomorrow morning, meet me there early.
And together, we'll fill the flower bed full of lilies before she arrives.
Okay.
But what if she...
I bet it will make Kureha so happy.
It'll be just like a magic fairy visited.
It's funny.
That girl would have done anything I said.
All I had to do was mention it was for Kureha.
Now come on.
Be honest with me, won't you?
The truth is, you found out that I was targeting Sumika Izumina, didn't you?
You should learn how to hide better.
I knew all along you were there.
Following Sumika to see what made her so great.
Will you get some?
They are very lovely.
What?
Oh, you're one of the new transfer students.
Hi.
Sniff, sniff.
They smell amazing.
I'm guessing you must be a fan of lilies, too.
I adore them.
They're lovely.
And they make me think of a special memory.
A special memory with a friend.
A friend I happen to love.
I won't back down on that love.
Because the love my friend gave me can't be taken away by anyone.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I bet it was weird for me to say something like that when we've only just met.
Yeah, you were jealous of her, weren't you?
The love you dreamed about and wanted so badly from Kareha had already been given to another girl.
And yet, you still wanted to see her again.
In fact, this time, you didn't even tell your partner what you were up to.
Why go?
Did you plan to warn her about me?
Yes.
That was the idea.
Oh, stupid me.
How could I go and lose the hairpin again?
Here.
Ginko!
You found it!
Thank you!
What a relief.
I'm so silly.
This is the second time someone's found this pin for me.
I lost it the day of the entrance ceremony, too.
The friend I told you about yesterday?
She's the one who found it before.
Neat, huh?
She found it for you before?
Yep.
This hairpin has brought me friendship and love.
I like to think of it as my special charm.
Thank you.
It means so much to me.
I really, really appreciate it, Ginko.
Now I'd better hurry up and run or I'll be late.
Where?
I was first, though.
She found me first.
Growl, growl.
That's right.
If you had gone ahead and stopped her then, Sumika Izumino wouldn't have had to die.
Koreha Tsubaki wouldn't have had to lose her very best friend, either.
I know.
I couldn't help it.
Sumika was in my way.
And we exclude those in our way.
It would be so much easier if we were just honest about what we want.
So that's the truth.
I'm guilty.
I wanted Sumika to die.
Well, good morning, Sumika.
Such a lovely morning.
And I'm practically starving.
You witnessed me attacking sweet little Sumika.
And you just sat there and watched.
You allowed her to die.
You could have saved her.
But you didn't.
Technically, yes, I'm the one who ate her.
But who was the one that really killed her?
It was me.
Indeed it was.
In that moment, you were a slave of desire.
Jealousy got a hold of you and drove you to a terrible crime.
I'm a criminal there.
Grow, grow.
Yes.
However, is there really any creature that doesn't sin in order to live?
Koreha Tsubaki forgot you.
Her friend.
And then she gave her love to Sumika instead.
Now, pay attention.
Only one thing in this world is certain.
And believe you me, it's not friendship or love.
Desire is the only thing you can count on, dear Ginkgo.
Love is a savage emotion.
To love another is to rule them.
To want to become one with them so badly you consume them is truly cruel.
I know something else you might want to hear, shall I tell you.
There's another bear at that school besides us.
A very cunning bear at that.
She got Koreha to kill me.
And she got Lulu Yurigasaki to betray you.
I hate to admit it, but that bitch bear had all of us dancing to her own little tune.
Everything she's done is because she's after Koreha.
If you don't hurry and stop her, you'll lose Koreha forever this time.
Are you ready to become one with me, Ginkgo?
The time has come to prove your love.
Grow, grow, grow, grow, grow!
Grow!
I'm going to eat her.
I have to grow, grow, grow, grow.
These photos were totally discovered in the locker of Kaoru Harishima,
who recently, like, way died in a bear attack.
Konami Yurikawa, as you can see, was actually a bear disguised as a human girl.
This is scary, like, way.
Bears got across the wall pretending to be human.
And they've, like, way eaten our friends one after the other.
We all see what this like means, don't we?
That's right, there's, like, a bear in this class.
A bear hiding among us, like, for real.
Bears, like, way stick out from our crowd.
Bears refuse to, like, fit in with us.
Bears are evil and can't follow social cues.
Here we go.
They've started up again.
Yep.
But, Kureha Tsubaki is attending the meeting this time.
They made her a friend at this late date?
Very interesting.
Have they canceled her exclusion then?
Ah, who can tell?
Those girls are always looking for some evil to exclude.
Doesn't matter to them whether the evil is a person or a bear or even really evil.
The ritual of banding together to exclude someone
is what makes the invisible connection they like to call us
feel as if it's real to them.
It looks like they're almost there.
For that is sexy.
Shabbat-dod-do.
Shall I put in another coin?
Yeah.
Shabbat-dod-do.
Let us now begin the exclusion ceremony.
Please name whom we think the bear lurking among us is.
Let's search bear!
People who like shelter bears are accomplices!
Tell me, Mom.
Did I...
Did I do the right thing that day?
Lulu.
Curry pie, Lulu knows the truth.
She found out what Ginko did to Sumika.
Yes, Ginko committed a grave crime, Growl.
Ginko is why Sumika's dead!
She helped the killer!
Ginko, is that true?
Yes, it's true, Growl, Growl.
I killed Sumika Izumino.
It was me!
Mitsuko Yurizono killed Sumika.
I know that for a fact, so...
Why would Ginko confess to it?
What's the truth and what's a lie?
I don't understand any of this.
Ball.
Yes?
This call is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki.
If your love is true, go to the Lily Bird immediately.
The bear in question will be waiting for you.
She's at the flower pit?
Ginko's waiting for me?
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
I'm going to go talk to Ginko.
And this time, I'm going to find out what really happened.
Huh.
To think she masqueraded as us
to make a prank call to Kureha Tsubaki.
Oh, that Yuri Ika Hakonaka.
She is guilty.
Mm-hmm.
Although, what she's about to do
is why she made the contract with us to begin with.
So, she's probably ready for the consequences.
Sparkle, sparkle.
All shall be as according to Kumaria's will.
For that is sexy.
Shabba da do.
Ginko.
What happened between us?
I want to know the truth.
Dearest Raya,
do you remember that stormy night?
Do you remember the moment I ate you?
Do you remember when I put you in the box of myself
to fill in my gaps?
But I wasn't fulfilled.
I was still so empty.
I figured out why, though.
It was because you had given all your love away to her.
So I decided to wait.
Until now.
I waited until that girl who stole your love from me
finally grew up.
And I waited as your love gradually and beautifully
blossomed inside of her.
I did all this in a blank world robbed of color.
I waited.
And waited.
At last.
Yes.
The flower has bloomed.
Today, I will eat your daughter.
Today, I will eat Koreha Tsubaki.
Ginko, where are you?
It...
This... this is wrong!
That bear isn't Ginkgo!
Oh, Rhea, she looks just like you.
Her eyes, her hair...
She even has your smell.
Kureha Tsubaki, give your love to me!
You and I are going to become one forever!
Take my kiss now, Kureha, my darling.
This kiss is a special one.
It's for my precious bride-in-the-box.
That was like a way super close call.
Choco? Oh...
The bear ran away! After it!
Wait, that's...
Eureka!
Rhea, you found me again.
I missed you so much.
Oh, how I've longed to see you just one more time, and here you are.
It's all I've dreamed about since that awful night I ate you.
Oh, Rhea.
I've been holding on to something precious I need to return to you.
In a box, in the middle of my drawers.
The moon girl and the forest girl.
That box has the rest of your picture book in it.
It was the dream of our love that never materialized.
I couldn't seem to help myself I wanted it so desperately I stole it.
Please forgive me.
Yes, you're right.
That will be their destiny.
Their rightful future.
You know the truth, don't you, Rhea?
You know how I feel.
I think you knew before I did.
And I still do.
And we'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes, forever and ever.
I love you.
I can't believe Miss Yuriyika was the bear that killed mom.
That will be their destiny.
Their rightful future.
Here it is.
The end.
Ginkgo's in my future?
It can't be.
That's impossible.